A special event was organised by ICICI Lombard in Patna as part of a
CSR initiative in
which senior officers of Bihar Police
participated.
DGP Vinay Kumar IPS, ADGP
Traffic Sudhanshu Kumar IPS and DIG
Sushant Saroj IPS were present as the chief guests in the program.
This event took place at Patel Bhawan Bihar Police Headquarters.
Where
emphasis was laid on aspects related to social responsibility and public interest.
Road safety is a big
responsibility for all of us and we all
should contribute to it.  In the same sequence, the government
is continuously trying to provide resources to the traffic police.  At
the same time, the
companies working in the corporate sector also
want to contribute in this matter through CSR funding.  In the same sequence,
today Viceard
provided traffic control regulations, which are barricades, road barricades and steel foldable barricades and
for which I thank them.
In the past years also, he has
contributed a lot in the field of safety and security through CSR party and he is
continuously working in this direction, so I
congratulate him for this and
hope
that all our stakeholders in road safety should
realize their responsibility and they should continuously work in that direction
so that we have safe and smooth traffic in the state of Bihar,
Sir
just saw
what all
things I told you,
he said in his address there,
how the scope of traffic police has
increased and now the traffic police is working in all the districts,
in how many
districts it has been deployed,
he threw light on all these things and after that he made us
aware of our responsibility that
we
Sachin, thank you.